NICOLÒ TREBINO

University student

Contact Information

+39 345 4149604

nicolo.trebino@gmail.com

nicolotrebino.com

github.com/nicolotrebino

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nicolò-trebino-624620303/

Key Skills and Projects

COMMUNICATIONS AND TEAMWORK

- · Collaboration with small student teams, excellent communication and interpersonal skills developed in university settings
- · Strong explanatory skills and a propensity for listening, acquired through coaching and tutoring
- · Excellent analytical skills gained through work experience
- · Ability to collaborate with professionals across diverse fields, expanding my network, acquired through academic activities and extra projects

UNIVERSITY-ACQUIRED SKILLS & PROJECTS

· GitHub: lisp Interpreter

· GitHub: FN-Org/RIOT:scheduler feedback

C, Operating systems

· GitHub: FN-Org/WikiSAW

Teamwork, project management, databases, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, web development, full-stack development

· GitHub: UE Chess

Unreal Engine, C++, algorithms

· GitHub: FN-Org/BellApp

Teamwork, Kotlin, Android, Android Studio, mobile application

· GitHub: FN-Org/BellsController

C, IoT, Arduino, Arduino IDE, STM32, STM32 Cube IDE, ESP32

· VS, VS Code

SELF-TAUGHT SKILLS

- · AutoCAD and 3D modeling
- · GitHub: FN-Org/Hack4Ge

Python, cybersecurity

- · Operating Systems: Windows, MacOS e Linux
- · WebStorm (JetBrains)
- · PHP Storm (JetBrains)
- · Rider (JetBrains)
- · Microsoft Office Suite

LANGUAGES

- · Italian (Native)
- · English (Fluent)
- · French (Basic)

Personal Statement

Italian computer engineering graduate pursuing a Master's in Al.

Passionate about technology, with experience in mobile apps, websites, and Unreal Engine game development.

Also a volleyball coach, promoting inclusivity through sitting volleyball.

Always willing to learn and face new challenges.

Key Experiences

PYTHON PROGRAMMING INSTRUCTOR

High School (Scientific, Classical, and Linguistic) - Liceo Da Vigo Nicoloso Rapallo Teaching materials and exercises available on GitHub: python programming course February 2024 - Present

VOLLEY USCIO FERRADA

- Under 13. Under 15 and Under 16 Volleyball Coach for Volley Uscio 2024 - Present

TREBINO S.N.C.

- AutoCAD design and 3D modeling for corporate projects
- Manual mechanical processes
- Social media management
- Digital Transformation & Technical Support

2024 - Present

TUTORING

- Tutoring for high school and technical institute students in scientific subjects 2021 - Present

PRO RECCO VOLLEYBALL

- Under 13 Volleyball Coach for Pro Recco Volleyball

Academic Background

MASTER DEGREE, **COMPUTER ENGINEERING: ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE** AND HUMAN-CENTERED COMPUTING

Università degli Studi di Genova

2024 - Present

BACHELOR DEGREE COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Università deali Studi di Genova

110 / 110 cum laude

2021 - 2024

SCIENTIFIC HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Nicoloso da Recco Scientific High School, Recco

98 / 100

2016 - 2021

Awards and other activities

HACK4GE

1st place, Cyber Security Hackathon in Genoa Development of a prototype capable of detecting vulnerabilities (SQLI and SSTI)

MERIT-BASED REWARDS

I was granted a tuition fee reduction for achieving a high GPA during my first and second year of university.

Academic Year 2021/2022, 2022/2023

ENGLISH C1 ADVANCED COURSE

Completed the My English School course and obtained certification for EXPERT 1 English level.

2023 - 2024

FIPAV SMART COACH

Certification as a first-level volleyball instructor by FIPAV Obtained in 2022

VOGLIO FARE IL MANAGER!

A great opportunity for growth and training, including experience working alongside managers from large local and international companies, specifically at Ericsson R&D and Boero Group HR and IT in Genoa. Nicho Telino

2024